// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "In cricket, what is the highest individual score ever made in a Test match?",
    answer: "400",
    options: [
      "375",
      "400",
      "500",
      "600"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which team won the 2019 Cricket World Cup?",
    answer: "England",
    options: [
      "England",
      "India",
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the name of the highest individual award in football (soccer)?",
    answer: "Ballon d'Or",
    options: [
      "Golden Boot",
      "Ballon d'Or",
      "Golden Ball",
      "FIFA World Player of the Year"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which team won the UEFA Champions League in the 2020-21 season?",
    answer: "Chelsea",
    options: [
      "Manchester City",
      "Paris Saint-Germain",
      "Chelsea",
      "Bayern Munich"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "In cricket, what is the term used for a dismissal where the bowler gets the batsman out without the ball being touched by the bat or any part of the batsman's body?",
    answer: "Bowled",
    options: [
      "Stumped",
      "Bowled",
      "Caught",
      "Run out"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the name of the most prestigious domestic cricket tournament in England?",
    answer: "County Championship",
    options: [
      "County Championship",
      "T20 Blast",
      "Royal London One-Day Cup",
      "Vitality Blast"
    ]
	},
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which team won the FIFA World Cup in 2018?",
    answer: "France",
    options: [
      "Brazil",
      "Germany",
      "France",
      "Spain"
    ]
	},
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "In cricket, what is the name of the tournament that features the top international teams playing in a round-robin format?",
    answer: "World Cup",
    options: [
      "World Cup",
      "T20 World Cup",
      "Champions Trophy",
      "Super Series"
    ]
	},
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the name of the famous football (soccer) stadium located in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil?",
    answer: "Maracanã",
    options: [
      "Maracanã",
      "Camp Nou",
      "Santiago Bernabéu",
      "Wembley Stadium"
    ]
	
	},
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who is the all-time leading scorer in the UEFA Champions League?",
    answer: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
    options: [
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Robert Lewandowski",
      "Raúl"
    ]
  },
 
];